

52, 11th Main Road
Banashankari Stage II
Bengaluru, INDIA 560070
▼ WHC9+8C BSK

**&** +91 97398 56528

್ಲಿ varungupta3009

## Experience



#### **Penetration Tester**

Center for Information Security, Forensics and Cyber Resilience May 2020 - Present (4 mos)



Student Lead in Network Security and Web Development

Developer Student Clubs • PES University Jan 2019 – Present (1 yr 8 mos)



#### **Software Engineer**

Mindtree

Jul 2019 - Feb 2020 (8 mos)

## Education



# PES University

Bachelor of Technology, Computer Science & Engineering 2017 – 2021



#### R. V. PU College

Pre-University, Affiliated to NCERT, New Delhi, Computer Science 2015 – 2017



#### Carmel School, Padmanabhanagar

ICSE, New Delhi — SSLC, Karnataka 2002 - 2015

## **Publications & Awards**

Software Implementation of an Automatic Movable Road Barrier IEEE, October 2019, ISBN: 978-1-7281-1576-4

Prof. C N R Rao Merit Scholarship

PES University, November 2019

### Licenses and Certifications

**Associate Cloud Engineer** 

Google, August 2020

## Languages

English Hindi Kannada

### Hobbies

□ Reading

X Virtual Aviation



Skill

## Knowledge and Skills

Experience	
Skill	
<b>JavaScript</b> Experience Skill	
C/C++ Experience Skill	
<b>Java, C#, Go</b> Experience Skill	
Frontend De Experience Skill	sign and Development
Full-Stack W Experience Skill	eb Development
	, React (JS/TS)
WordPress, e Experience Skill	
Experience	oshop & Illustrator
Skill  Adobe After  Experience	Effects and Premiere Pro
Skill	ar Renderman
Experience Skill	ar Refluerman
Cloud Archit	echture (GCP)

### About me

I am a programmer and experienced web-developer, fluent in Python, C++, C#, Go with over 9 years of experience in Python and C++, and moderately versed in 7 other languages. I am a polymath and love to explore and try new technologies and fiddling with anything related to computers or the Windows OS in general. I am also a graphics designer and a hobbyist hacker.

I recommend checking out my LinkedIn Profile for real-time accurate information, to stay regularly updated and get in touch with me instantly.

